It's so weird. How did Joey end up kissing Charlie last night?
真是太奇怪了 喬伊昨晚最後怎麼會去親查莉呢？
- I thought you'd end up kissing Charlie. - I thought I'd end up kissing Charlie too.
-我還以為最後會是你去親查莉 -我也這麼以為啊
But surprise!
但是…驚喜！
I missed most of the party.
我錯過大部分的派對
Charlie's a girl, right?
查莉是女生，對吧？
Yeah, she's this new professor in my department that I did not kiss.
是的，她是剛到繫上來 而我沒親到的那個新教授
I don't know why Joey had to kiss her. Of all the girls at the party, God!
我不知道為什麼喬伊要親她 有這麼多女生在派對上，天啊！
- Why do you care so much? - Yes, Rachel. Why do you care so much?
-你為什麼這麼在乎呢？ -是啊，瑞秋，你為什麼這麼在乎呢？
Because Ross is the father of my child.
因為羅斯是我孩子的父親
You know, and I want him to hook up with lots of women.
你知道的，而我希望他可以有機會 跟很多女人交往
All I'm saying is, I don't think that Joey and Charlie have anything in common.
我的意思是說，我不認為喬伊跟查莉 有任何相同之處
I don't know. They seemed to have a shared interest in each other's tonsils.
我不知道，他們似乎對彼此的扁桃腺 有相同的興趣
Wow. Joey and a professor. Can you imagine if they had kids?
哇，喬伊跟大學教授 你們能想像萬一他們有小孩嗎？
And if the kids got her intelligence..
如果小孩子遺傳到她的智慧…
and Joey's raw sexual magnetism..
還有喬伊的原始性吸引力…
those nerds would get laid!
書獃子還可以隨時來一跑！
All right. So, Ross, you're okay with all this? I mean..
好了，羅斯你對這一切都沒關係嗎？ 我是說…
It's no big deal. I just met her. I'm fine with it.
又沒有什麼大不了的，我才剛認識她 我沒事的
God, I forgot how hot she was.
天啊，我忘了她有多辣了
I'm gonna get some more coffee.
我要去多倒些咖啡
- Oh, you know, I'll come with you. - Okay.
-喔，我跟你去 -好的
- So a professor, huh? - Yeah. She is cool. And she's so smart.
-是教授嗎？ -是啊，她真酷，而且很聰明
Her mind is totally acrimonious.
她的內心是完全的「尖酸刻薄」
Guess that's not how she used it.
她好像不是那樣用那個字的
I feel like I owe you an explanation.
我覺得我應該向你解釋…
I don't ordinarily go around kissing guys at parties.
我通常不會在派對上亂親男生的
I'm..
我…
Well, I'm kind of embarrassed. I really hope you don't think less of me.
嗯，我有點難為情 我希望你不會因此而瞧不起我
Think less of you? No. I don't think less of you.
瞧不起你？我不會瞧不起你的
I mean, you saw someone you liked and you kissed them.
我是說，你看到喜歡的人 然後你親了他
Those people who like someone and don't kiss them..
那些有喜歡的人 卻又不親他們的人…
those people are stupid. I hate those people.
那些人是笨蛋，我恨死那些人了
Actually, I'm a little surprised at myself.
事實上，我自己也是很驚訝
I mean, Joey's so different from the guys I usually date.
我是說，喬伊跟我以前 交往的人太不同了
They're all professors, intellectuals. Paleontologists mostly.
他們全都是教授、高知識份子 大部分是古生物學家
- You know, very cerebral.. - Yeah, I know the type.
-你知道的，非常有理智… -是的，我知道那一類型的人
If we want to grab a bite before work, we'd better get acrimonious.
如果你想要在上班前先吃點東西 我們最好趕快尖酸刻薄
No? Am I getting close?
不對嗎？意思很接近吧？
The One With The Fertility Test
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
- Hey! - Hi.
-嘿！ -嗨
Hey, you guys. Look what I just got.
嘿，你們瞧瞧我買了什麼
Oh, wow! I love those! Where did you get them?
哇！我喜歡這雙鞋！ 你去哪買的？
I bought them off eBay. They used to belong to the late Shania Twain.
我從拍賣網站上買的 這本來屬於已過世的順子的
Phoebe, Shania Twain is still alive.
菲比，順子還活著
Oh, then I overpaid.
喔，那我被坑了
Hey, what's this?
嘿，這是什麼？
Oh, it's a gift certificate to this new spa in SoHo.
喔，那是蘇活區一間 新開水療中心的禮券
You can't show Phoebe this. She hates those corporate massage chains.
你不能給菲比看到 她痛恨這些大型連鎖按摩中心的
What, now I can't get a massage?
什麼？我連按摩都不行嗎？
There are so many things that she disapproves of.
有很多事情她都不准我們做
I can't eat veal. I can't wear fur.
我不能吃犢牛肉，我不能穿皮草
I can't go hunting.
我不能去打獵
- Do you want to go hunting? - I would like to have the option.
-你想要去打獵嗎？ -至少我要有選擇的權利
What's that? Hey, Rachel?
那是什麼？嘿，瑞秋？
No, you can't go there!
不，你不能去！
You know how I feel about these big massage places.
你知道我對這些按摩中心的觀感
They're putting people like me out of business.
它們害得像我這樣的人失業
She wants to go hunting too!
她也想去打獵喔！
Phoebe, come on, I don't want to waste it.
菲比，別這樣，我不想浪費掉它
It would be like throwing away 100 bucks.
這就好像是白白丟掉一百塊
Okay, this is not about the money. Okay?
這跟錢無關，好嗎？？
It's about corporate greed destroying our hearts..
這跟大企業貪婪毀滅我們的心靈…
and leaving us hollow shells.
然後讓我們只剩下 空空的軀體有關
I don't care about any of that.
我根本不在乎那些
Well, do you care about friendship? I feel really strongly about this.
那你在乎我們的友誼嗎？ 我對這個真的很反感
Please don't use this gift certificate. I'm asking you as a friend.
請不要用這張禮券 我以朋友的身份要求你
Oh, not as a friend. Phoebe!
喔，不要以朋友的身份，菲比！
Fine. I won't use it.
好啦，我不用就是了
- Promise? - I promise.
-保證嗎？ -我保證
- Thank you. - Well, I am going hunting.
-謝謝 -不過我會去打獵的
Hey, honey. I missed you today.
嗨，親愛的，我今天好想你
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah. Hey.
-喔，是嗎？ -是啊
- What do you wanna do tonight? - Oh, well, maybe we could..
-你今晚想要做什麼呢？ -或許我們可以…
Okay, trying to turn me on by making a mess?
好，想用把東西弄亂 來讓我性奮嗎？
Know your audience.
多瞭解一下你的對象
Besides, tomorrow we're doing those fertility tests.
況且，明天我們要做不孕症的檢查
Until then, you need to keep your tadpoles in the tank.
在那之前 你得要把你的蝌蚪放在池塘裡
Do we really need to take those tests?
我們一定要做那些檢查嗎？
I don't like the words they use, you know?
我不喜歡他們用的 那些字眼，你知道嗎？
They're so clinical. This is a pee-pee, that's a hoo-hoo.
太醫學化了 這是小弟弟，那是小妹妹
We've been trying to have a baby for a year.
我們為了要懷孕已經試了一年了
I think it's a good idea to find out if everything's okay.
我認為檢查一切是否正常 是件好事
- Just a few routine tests. - But I don't want to do it in a cup.
-只是幾樣例行的檢查 -但是我不想要弄在一個杯子裡
- What is the big deal? - It's weird! You're in a doctor's office.
-有什麼大不了的呢？ -很怪！在診所裡
It's not okay to do it in a doctor's office..
不能在診所做…
but it is okay to do it in a parked car behind a Taco Bell?
但是在頂呱呱後面的 停車場就可以嗎？
I cannot believe Ross told you that.
我不敢相信羅斯告訴了你
And in my defense, it was a Wendy's.
但是我要澄清的是 那是在溫蒂漢堡
Look, I don't want to do these tests either.
聽著，我也不想做那些檢查
But I really do think it's a good idea.
但是我真的認為這是個好主意
I'm sure a doctor's office can't be worse..
我想在醫院做總不會比…
than on a class trip to the Hershey factory.
在去巧克力工廠的 遠足上做還糟糕吧？
Oh, yeah! Rachel talks too!
喔，是的！ 瑞秋也是大嘴巴！
Who says wine has to cost more than milk?
誰說酒一定要比牛奶貴呢？
- Hey! - Hi.
-嘿！ -嗨
- Come on in. How are you? - I'm good.
-請進，你好嗎？ -我很好
- Can I offer you a drink? - Please.
-你要喝一杯嗎？ -麻煩了
I have been crazed all day.
我整天都忙瘋了
I had a meeting with the dean, my syllabus for summer school's due..
我跟系主任開了會 我暑期班的課程表又要交…
and I'm writing the foreword for a book.
然後我要幫一個朋友寫新書的序
I had a pretty hectic day at work too. Today I had to open a door and go:
我今天工作也很忙 今天我要開門然後做…
So I am just so excited to be here.
所以我很興奮能夠來到這裡
- I can't wait to explore the city. - If you need a tour guide..
-我等不及要發掘這個城市了 -如果你需要導遊…
Oh, you mean it? That would be so fun.
你是說真的嗎？一定會很好玩
Oh, yeah, definitely. Definitely. Okay. What do you want to see first?
喔，是一定的 好了，你想先去哪裡呢？
We could go see the Kronos Quartet at Avery Fisher Hall.
我們可以去國家音樂廳聽 克諾斯四重奏
Okay.
好的
There's a collection of Walt Whitman letters on display at the public library.
在市立圖書館有惠特曼書信的展覽
I know.
我知道
- But first, I have to see the Met. - Okay, let me stop you right there.
-但是，我想先去看看大都會博物館 -好的，讓我先打斷一下…
The Mets suck, okay?
大都會隊遜斃了，好嗎？
You wanna see the Yankees.
你會比較喜歡洋基隊的
No. No, not the Mets. The Met. Singular.
不，不是大都會隊 是大都會，是單數
Which one? They all suck.
那一隊？反正他們 全部都很遜
The museum.
博物館
I don't think so.
我可不認為這一隊 會好到哪裡去
- Hi there. - Hello. Welcome to Lavender Day Spa.
-嗨 -哈囉，歡迎光臨薰衣草芳香療法
How may I help you?
我能為您服務嗎？
Hi. I have a massage appointment under Rachel Greene.
嗨，我是瑞秋葛林，我有預約按摩
- Okay. - And here is my gift certificate.
-好的 -這是我的禮券
- This has been torn up. - And taped back together.
-這被撕掉了 -而且被黏回去了
Okay. Well, I'll call you as soon as your massage therapist is ready.
好的，等您的按摩師準備好後 我會馬上通知您的
- Okay. - Have a seat through the glass doors.
-好的 -請在玻璃門外的沙發坐一下
- Through the glass doors. - Through the glass doors.
-在玻璃門外 -在玻璃門外
All righty then.
好的
Phoebe, your next client's in the waiting room.
菲比，你的下一位客人 在候客室等著
Do we have to talk like that when they're not around?
當客人不在的時候 我們也要這樣說話嗎？
Oh, no. No, no.
喔，不不不…
Listen, is there someone who can fill in for me?
聽著，有人可以幫我做這一個嗎？
- Sorry. Everyone is booked. - That woman can't know I work here.
-對不起，大家都被預約了 -那女人不能知道我在這裡工作
She's a friend of mine and I made this big stink..
她是我朋友，而我告訴她我很討厭…
about how awful these massage chains are.
這些糟糕的按摩連鎖店
- Then why do you work here? - Because it's good money.
-那你為什麼要在這裡工作呢？ -因為薪水很好啊！
But that doesn't change the fact..
但是那並不會改變…
that this is an evil, bloodsucking corporate machine.
這是個邪惡、吸血、大企業體的事實
Well, I think this is a great place to work.
我倒是覺得這是個不錯的工作環境
Okay, are they listening?
好，他們有在聽嗎？
- Ross. Hey. - Hi.
-羅斯 -嗨
I need to talk to you about Charlie.
我需要跟你談查莉的事
Oh, do you? Do you really?
喔，真的嗎？ 有必要嗎？
Yeah, I'm kind of having a little problem.
是啊，我有一點小問題…
Look, if you don't know what the word "acrimonious" means, just don't use it.
聽著，如果你不知道「尖酸刻薄」 是什麼意思，那就不要用它
Look, you know Charlie, right?
聽著，你瞭解查莉，不是嗎？
- She's cool, funny, her body is so.. - Get to the problem.
-她很酷、風趣，而且她的身材又很… -說重點
Right. She's just so much smarter than all the girls I've ever dated.
好的，她只是比我約會過的 所有女生全部加起來
Combined.
都還要聰明
You know? And I just.. I don't want her to think I'm stupid.
你知道嗎？而我只是… 我不想要讓她覺得我很笨
Are you wearing two belts?
你系兩條皮帶嗎？
Hey, what do you know?
嘿，誰知道呢？
You were saying you didn't want to seem stupid.
你剛剛說你不想看起來很笨
Well, she wants to go to all these cultural places..
嗯，她想要去那些 很有文化的地方…
and I don't know how to talk about that stuff. You gotta help me out.
而我不知道要怎麼談論那些東西 你一定要幫我
I don't want to get involved in your guys' relationship.
我不想要介入你們的關係當中
Oh, dude, please. Come on, you're the smartest person I know.
老兄，拜託，別這樣 你是我認識最聰明的人
And I really like this girl, okay? I don't want to lose her.
而我真的很喜歡這個女生，好嗎？ 我不想要失去她
- Fine. - Thanks.
-好啦 -謝謝
Okay. Let's see.
好的，讓我想想…
- Oh, you should take her to the Met. - The Mets.
-喔，你應該帶她去大都會 -大都會隊
No, no, no. The Met. The Metropolitan Museum of Art.
不，大都會 大都會藝術博物館
Oh, that's what she meant.
喔，原來她指的是那個
If they're gonna shorten it, they should call it the "Muse, " you know?
如果他們要用簡稱，應該把它 叫做「博物」，你知道嗎？
Short for "museum" and avoid all the confusion.
博物館的簡稱，避免混淆
Yeah, most days the place is packed with confused, angry baseball fans.
是啊，很多時候那地方都擠滿了混淆 又生氣的棒球迷
Okay. All right, so I'll take her to the Met.
好的，那我帶她去大都會
Yeah. Okay. There's this great rare bookstore on Madison Avenue.
對了，在麥迪遜大道上 有間很棒的書店
You know what? She loves architecture.
你知道嗎？她熱愛建築
You should take a walk down Fifth to the St. Patrick's Cathedral.
你應該帶她從第五大道散步 到聖派屈克教堂
And there, there's this great little pastry shop that she'd love.
在那邊有間很棒的烘培坊 她一定會喜歡
Jeez. Sounds like you should be going on this date.
天啊，聽起來好像 是你應該去約會才對
But I'm not.
但是我並沒有
- And you know what..? - Okay, slow down.
-而你知道嗎？ -好的，說慢一點
You're going way too fast. Okay? Just go back to the Met.
你說的太快了，好嗎？ 先回去講大都會
So you gotta tell me exactly what to do there.
你必須要詳細告訴我在那邊要做什麼
When you walk into the museum, take a right, okay?
當你們進入博物館時，先向右轉…
That's the antiquities wing.
那邊是古代文物廳
Ancient Egypt, Mesopotamia, up to the Byzantine Empire.
古埃及、美索不達米亞直到 拜占庭帝國
Okay. So I walk in the door and make a right.
好的，所以我進門以後 往右轉…
I have a weird feeling about this place. How do I know..
我覺得這地方怪怪的，我怎麼知道…
they won't secretly videotape me and put it all over the lnternet?
他們會不會偷錄下來 然後放到網路上呢？
Because, honey, and I mean this in the sweetest way possible..
因為，親愛的… 我以我能做到最甜美的方式告訴你…
nobody's gonna wanna watch that.
沒有人會想要看的
Mr. Bing? Here you are.
賓先生？拿去吧
Go into that room and deposit your specimen into the container.
進去那間房間，然後把樣本放入容器內
Deposit my specimen?
把樣本放入？
I usually have to call a 900 number for that kind of talk.
我通常要打一些900電話 才能聽到這種談話
Thanks. Got it.
謝謝，知道了
All right. Honey, my tests are down the hall.
好了，親愛的 我的檢查在另外一邊
- Are you sure you're gonna be okay? - Yeah, I guess.
-你確定你還好嗎？ -是的，我想應該吧
Look, I know this is embarrassing, but nobody cares.
聽著，我知道這很尷尬 但是沒有人在乎啊
No one here even knows you.
在這裡根本沒有人認識你
Oh, my God!
喔，我的天啊！
Oh, come on!
喔，不會這麼倒霉吧！
How great is this?
這是不是太棒了呢？
We're probably fertile. Let's go home.
我們或許沒有不孕，我們回家吧
Why are you here?
你會什麼會在這裡呢？
Sid and I are trying again and we had trouble last time..
西德跟我想要再試一次 我們上一次有問題…
No, no, no. I mean, why? Why is she here?
不，我是說，為什麼？ 為什麼她會在這裡？
Oh, someone's a little cranky today because they have to do it in a cup.
有人今天不太高興因為他們要 弄到一個杯子裡面…
Oh, they gave you the kiddie size.
喔，他們給你小朋友的杯子
What?
什麼？
This was fun. But I've got an invasive vaginal exam to get to.
這真有趣，但是我有內診要去做
I'd love to stay but I've got a hot date.
我也希望我可以留下來 但是我有個火辣的約會
Please go. Just let me know if you need a hand.
請便，讓我知道一下如果你需要幫手
I think it just fell off.
我想它剛剛掉了
Hello, ja.
哈囉 是的
It's time for your massage, ja?
按摩時候到了，是的
Put your face in the hole.
把你的臉放入洞中
A Swedish massage from a real Swedish person.
真正瑞典人做的瑞典式按摩
Okay, then I'm Swedish.
好的，那我就是瑞典人
So, what's your name?
你叫什麼名字呢？
It's a normal Swedish name.
只是平凡一般的瑞典名字
Ikea.
宜家
- Wow. What an interesting name. - Yeah.
-哇，真是有趣的名字 -是啊
- You know, I.. - Time for your scalp massage.
-你知道，我… -頭皮按摩時間到了
Wow. I really love your..
哇，我真的好喜歡你的…
- Is something wrong? - No, it's just..
-有什麼不對嗎？ -不，只是…
It just feels so good..
只是覺得很舒服…
Ikea.
宜家
Hey, say, you'll know this. What's the capital of Sweden?
嘿，看你知不知道這個 瑞典的首都是哪裡呢？
Stockholm.
斯德哥爾摩
Damn. I wish I knew if that was right.
該死的，希望我知道那是對還是錯
Note the painterly lines and subtle impasto on this canvas.
看那些線條，潛藏多層顏料 厚塗在畫布上…
Monet painted quickly, and usually outdoors..
莫內快速地作畫，而且通常是在戶外…
as his elusive subject was light itself.
因為他和光線一樣喜歡孤獨
Now, do you have any idea what you just said?
你知道你剛剛說的是什麼意思嗎？
No, no. My mouth says the words, my brain is thinking "monster trucks."
不，我的嘴巴說著那些字 但是我的頭腦想的是「怪獸卡車」
Now, remember, when you get to the museum..
現在，記住，當你進入博物館時…
Monet is not spelled M-O-N-A-Y. I just..
莫內的寫法不是「內」 我只是…
- I wrote that out phonetically for you. - Phonetically?
-幫你用注音寫下來 -注音？
Yeah, that means.. We just don't have time for this.
是的，那是… 我們沒有時間討論那些了
I gotta say, I'm really impressed you were able to memorize all this so quickly.
我得說我真的很驚訝 你可以這麼快速背下這些東西
I'm an actor. I can memorize anything.
我是演員，我可以背下任何東西的
Last week on Days, I had to say:
上星期在《我們的日子》劇中 我得說：
"Frontal temporal zygomatic craniotomy."
「前端顳顴骨切開術」
- Wow. What does that mean? - No idea.
-哇，那是什麼意思呢？ -不知道
But the guy I said it to dies in the next scene..
但是那個被我那樣說的男的 在下一集就死了
so I guess it means, "You'll get eaten by a bear."
所以我想那可能是說 「你會被熊給吃了」
Okay.
好的
- So let's move on to the Renaissance. - Okay.
-那我們來看文藝復興時期 -好的
Caravaggio uses chiaroscuro here..
卡拉瓦喬在這裡使用了 明暗對照法…
to highlight the anguish of the central figure.
突顯出中央人物的極度痛苦
Touch it. It's really bumpy.
碰觸它，還真是凹凸不平
No, no, no. No ad-libbing. And, dude, you can't touch the paintings.
不，不能即興演出 還有，你不能亂碰這些畫作的
- Come on. - No. No!
-擔心什麼？ -不，不！
My specimen's in the room.
我的樣本在房間裡了
I just want to thank whoever knocked on the door while I was in there.
我只想謝謝剛剛那個 我在裡面的時候敲門的人…
Really helped speed the process along.
真的幫助加速了整個流程
Janice, you're not gone?
珍妮絲，你還沒有消失啊？
Sid is still in his room.
西德還在他的房間裡
I don't allow porn at home, so this is like a vacation for him.
我不許家裡有色情書刊 所以這對他而言簡直是快樂假期
So did you do it? Did you make your deposit?
所以你做了嗎？ 完成你的樣品存放手續了嗎？
- Yeah. The hard part's over. - That's not the hard part, honey.
-是啊，最困難的部份結束了 -那不是最困難的，親愛的
No, there's talking to you, but Monica's coming out.
沒錯啊，跟你說完了 摩妮卡出來了
And we're gonna go soon.
我們很快就要走了
Chandler.
錢德
The hard part's what comes next. Aren't you worried about the results?
接下來才是最困難的部份 你難道不擔心結果嗎？
I mean, oh, when Sid and I did this last time, my God, I was a mess.
我是說，當西德跟我上次來做的時候 我的天，我緊張死了
I haven't even thought about the results.
我根本沒有想過結果
I just assumed everything would be okay.
我只是以為一切都會沒事
Well, you know what? It probably is.
結果你知道嗎？或許就是沒事
But what if it's not okay?
但是要是有事呢？
I mean, what if there's a reason we can't have a baby?
我是說萬一我們不孕是有原因的呢？
Chandler. Look, you and Monica are meant to have children.
錢德，聽著，你跟摩妮卡一定會有小孩
I'm sure it's gonna be just fine.
我敢說一切一定都沒事的
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Thanks. I can't believe I didn't even think of that.
是啊，是啊，好了，謝謝 我不敢相信我竟然沒有想過
I guess I was so worried about having to come here and do that.
我是說我好擔心要過來這裡做檢驗
You can do it in a Taco Bell parking lot..
你可以在頂呱呱的停車場做…
but you can't do it at a doctor's office?
但是你沒有辦法在診所做嗎？
It was a Wendy's!
是溫蒂！
And that's the Swedish national anthem. Thank you for asking.
這就是瑞典國歌，謝謝你問了
Wow, Ikea.
哇，宜家家居
What a rich culture.
真是豐富的文化
You know what? I have a friend who's a masseuse.
你知道嗎？我有個朋友也是按摩師
- Oh? Ja, ja? - Ja. She's not very good, though.
-喔？是嗎？ -是啊，不過她不是很行
- And why do you think that is? - I don't know.
-你為什麼會那樣覺得呢？ -我不知道
Maybe it's because she's got such callousy fingers..
或許是因為她的手指很僵硬
from playing crummy guitar.
大概是彈爛吉他而來的
Or maybe she has trouble loosening your knots..
或許因為她很難放鬆你的筋骨
because you're such a high-maintenance tight-ass.
因為你真是個難搞的俏屁股
- Phoebe! - You know it's me?
-菲比！ -你知道是我？
Well, for like a half an hour!
嗯，知道半個小時了！
Man, you can lie about Sweden!
天啊，你還真能扯瑞典的事！
How can you come here?
你怎麼能夠到這裡來呢？
- Why didn't you tell me you work here? - I don't have to tell you everything!
-你為什麼沒說你在這裡工作呢？ -我不需要告訴你每件事！
You do if you're gonna make me feel guilty for getting a free massage.
如果你讓我覺得來這裡享受免費按摩 是很罪惡的事，那你就要
Tip's not included.
小費還是要照算的
Why did you lie to me about working here?
為什麼你不敢說你在這裡工作呢？
Because I was ashamed, okay? I sold out for the cash.
因為我覺得很丟臉，好嗎？ 我為五斗米而折腰
And they give me benefits, like medical and dental and a four-oh-wunk.
他們提供一些福利，像是健保什麼的
But, you know, you pay a price. Now I'm this corporate stooge..
但是你知道的，要付出代價的 現在我成了大公司的傀儡
and punching a clock..
每天打卡上班
and paying taxes!
然後還要繳稅！
Phoebe, honey, if you hate it so much..
菲比，親愛的，如果 你這樣痛恨這工作…
you should walk out there right now and quit.
你應該馬上走出去然後辭職
Be true to what you believe in.
相信你所堅信的理念
Honey, you have principles, and I so admire that.
親愛的，你是有原則的人 所以我很欽佩你的
I don't have any.
我才是沒有原則
You know what? You're right. I am gonna quit.
你知道嗎？你說的對，我要去辭職
- It's time I took my life back. - Good for you, Phoebe.
-該是我重新生活的時候了 -很好，菲比
If you guys have microphones in there too, I didn't mean any of that.
如果你們在裡面也有裝麥克風 我在裡面說的都不是真的
I love you.
我愛你們
Got you! Die! Die! Die!
打到了！死吧！死吧！死吧！
Respectfully, Professor R. Geller.
誠摯地，蓋勒教授敬上
- Hey. - Hi.
-嘿 -嗨
Hey, how was the Met?
嘿，大都會好玩嗎？
The museum was amazing.
博物館真的很驚人
Yeah, Joey really knows his art, huh?
是啊，喬伊真的很懂藝術不是嗎？
Not so much, no.
並不盡然，不
He had clearly memorized all this stuff to say..
很明顯地他清楚地背下了要說的東西…
and some of it didn't even make any sense.
但是很多東西都很不對勁
- What do you mean? - Well, for one..
-你是什麼意思呢？ -嗯，例如…
he was talking about paintings that were nowhere around.
他談論的都是根本不在展出的繪畫
Wait a minute. When you guys walked into the Met, did you go to the right?
等等，你們進入博物館之後 是往右邊走嗎？
- No. No, we went to the left. - Oh, Joey, Joey, Joey.
-不不，我們往左邊走 -喔，喬伊，喬伊，喬伊
Still, it seems like you guys are having a great time together.
可是你們看起來也是度過快樂的時光啊
Yeah. Yeah, it's fun.
是啊，是很好玩
What?
怎樣？
Actually, Joey's your friend..
事實上，喬伊是你的朋友…
and you don't know me that well. It'd be weird.
而你也不是很瞭解我 這會很奇怪的
Well, I mean, a little. But no, what? Go on.
嗯，可能會有點，但是不會啦 怎樣呢？跟我說
Well..
嗯…
I'm thinking that maybe Joey isn't the right guy for me right now.
我在想或許喬伊不是很適合我
You know, maybe I should be with someone..
你知道的，或許我應該跟…
I have more in common with. You know what I mean?
跟我比較相像的人在一起 你知道我的意思嗎？
Yeah.
是啊
Yeah, but you know what?
是啊，但是你知道嗎？
I think you should give Joey a chance.
我想你應該給喬伊一個機會
I mean, he's a great guy.
我是說他是個好男人
And sure, he doesn't know that much about art..
當然他是不知道很多藝術的東西
but you can always talk about that with someone else.
但是你可以跟其他知道的人談論啊
- I guess that's true. - If you think about it..
-我想也是 -如果你仔細想想…
he memorized all that stuff because he thought it was important to you.
他背下所有的東西只是因為 他認為那些東西對你很重要
You know, that's the kind of guy Joey is.
你知道的，喬伊就是那樣子的人
He is very sweet.
他是非常貼心的
Plus, he is hot!
還有，他真是帥斃了！
That was gonna be my next argument.
這就是我下一個要爭論的
- You ready? - Yeah. Let's go.
-你準備好了嗎？ -好了，我們走吧
Wow!
哇！
- Thanks, Ross. - Yeah.
-謝了，羅斯 -不客氣
Hey, Ross. That art stuff worked. You hooked me up.
嘿，羅斯，藝術那些東西真是有效 你真幫了大忙
Glad I could help, man.
很高興能夠幫上忙，兄弟
Some of the stuff wasn't where you said it would be, but I made it work.
有些你說的東西並沒有在那裡 但是我都搞定了
It is not okay that I'm aroused by this now.
我現在不能因為這個而勃起了
Hello?
哈囉？
Oh. Hi, Dr. Connelly.
喔，嗨，唐納利醫生
No. Well, she's not here..
不，她現在不在…
but I can tell her.
但是我可以轉告她
Should I be sitting down for this?
我應該先坐下來再聽嗎？
Well, so, what does that mean?
那，那是什麼意思呢？
Okay. Okay, thank you.
好的，好的，謝謝你
Thanks.
謝謝
Hey, sweetie.
嘿，親愛的
Dr. Connelly just called.
唐納利醫生剛剛打電話來
With good news? Of course it's not good news.
有好消息嗎？當然不是好消息囉
You said, "Dr. Connelly just called."
你是說「唐納利醫生剛剛打電話來」
If it was good, you'd have said, "Dr. Connelly just called!"
如果是好消息你會說 「唐納利醫生剛剛打電話來！」
So, what is it? Is it..?
那，是怎樣呢？是不是…
Is there a problem? Is there a problem with me, or with you?
有問題嗎？是我的問題還是你的呢？
Actually, it's both of us.
事實上我們兩個都有問題
What?
什麼？
Apparently, my sperm have low motility..
很顯然地，我的精子活動力太低了
and you have an inhospitable environment.
而你有不適著床的環境
Well, what does that mean?
喔，那是什麼意思呢？
It means that my guys won't get off their Barcaloungers..
意思就是說我的人根本沒有辦法出兵…
and you have a uterus that is prepared to kill the ones that do.
而你的子宮已準備好 要殺死入侵的小兵了
- It means.. - Wait, Chandler.
-意思是 -等等，錢德
It means that we can keep trying..
意思是我們可以繼續嘗試…
but there's a good chance this may never happen for us.
但是我們很有可能永遠都不會懷孕
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
我也很抱歉
Well..
嗯…
we're gonna figure this out.
我們會想出辦法的
I know.
我知道
- Good morning, Phoebe. - Good morning, receptionist.
-早安，菲比 -早安，總機小姐
Here's your schedule for the day. Your first client is in Room 1.
這是你今天的工作排程 你第一位客人在一號房
"Rachel Greene." Son of a bitch! She came back?
「瑞秋葛林」，狗娘養的！ 她又回來了？
Are you ready for your Scottish massage?
你準備好要享受蘇格蘭式按摩了嗎？
Put your face in the hole, lassie!
把臉放到洞中間 小妞！（蘇格蘭叫法）